So I have a real question for everybody out there who is running for Congress.
What makes you special?
What makes you, as an individual, special and able to dismantle a system that has been designed from inception to functionally be dysfunctional for the people?
You know, when I was in Tougaloo, a brother came up to me and was like, I'm running for Congress.
And I was like, OK. And and he was like, well, you know, I just want you to know, I will not take a cent of APAC money.
I will not take corporate money. Y'all, that's very basic.
I just want y'all to understand, like, that's like when a father says I pay child support.
Like, OK, should you get props for that?
So he went on speaking and I said, my question to you, though, is everything is I'm I'm I'm.
What are you doing to coalition build to be able to do any of the things that you're claiming that you want to do?
Because they're not going to let you do that. And I'm not speaking just about Republicans.
Democrats have actively prevented any type of diversion from upholding the corporatocracy and the oligarchy and the Zionism.
So how are you changing the ability to change that?
Well, we're going to fight. I said, what?
He said, we're going to fight. I said, oh, so you are a politician.
And he was like, you know what? It's been nice to meet you. I said, it's been mediocre to meet you.
This is what I'm talking about. Y'all know these elections are rigged.
So what are you doing to disrupt the rigoration ability?
Every one of you that I see saying I'm going to go in and I'm going to run for Congress and not announcing any other form of going into Congress other than you.
You all look to me like the same type of people who are going in here to try to be some savior and you are not able to do it alone.
So unless I see some coalition building that looks like something different than what the Democrats are doing, you're all cut from the same cloth.
And quite frankly, we need to cut it. Snip, snip, snip.
The United States has an unbreakable bond with Israel.
Israel is a true friend. It is our greatest ally in the region.
The International Criminal Court singles out Israel, but not Iran.
It's great to be here at the annual conference in support of the U.S.-Israel relationship.
A relationship that, of course, is anchored in our shared values.
Always also made clear that we continue to support Israel's right to defend itself.